

MUHAMMAD IQBAL Web Developer

Palembang, Indonesia

- ⊠ mhmd.iqbal1599@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/wd-mhmd-iqbal/
- O https://github.com/mhmd-iqbal

**** 0895323755721

https://porfolio-iqbal.netlify.app

SUMMARY

A web developer with 2+ years of experience in PHP and Javascript. Familiar with the concepts of MVC and OOP and also well-versed in using Git. Proficient in creating responsive, modern, and user-friendly websites using the Laravel and Bootstrap frameworks. Also experienced in using JavaScript and have worked on projects involving ReactJS. Currently, I am dedicated to learning NextJS. Frequently use MySQL, but also delved into NoSQL databases like MongoDB. I am confident that my skills make me a valuable asset wherever I am.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. CERMAT PRATAMA SEJAHTERA - Palembang, Indonesia

IT Support & Programmer (October 2022 – present)

- Creating responsive, dynamic, and modern web-based applications using PHP (native, Laravel), JavaScript (vanilla, jQuery, ReactJS), and Bootstrap for internal company use.
- Designing and building databases for applications.
- Performing maintenance and development on existing web applications.
- Establishing collaboration proposals with other institutions/companies for the creation of web-based applications.
- Identifying and resolving internet network issues.
- Conducting computer hardware maintenance and repairs.

Jokiweb - Palembang, Indonesia

Freelance Web Developer (December 2021 - present)

- Responsible for creating dynamic and responsive web applications according to client requests.
- Focuses on projects that use the Laravel and CodeIgniter framework.

PHYLOT SYSTEM INTEGRATOR - Palembang, Indonesia

Back-end Web Developer (January 2022 - March 2022)

 Responsible for creating dynamic and responsive web applications using the PHP CodeIgniter framework to integrate with automated parking controllers.

EDUCATION

POLITEKNIK NEGERI SRIWIJAYA (2017 - 2020)

Associate Degree in Computer Engineering - GPA 3.38

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- PHP (Laravel, CodeIgniter)
- JavaScript (jQuery, Node.js, ReactJS, NextJS)
- AJAX
- MySQL, MongoDB
- Git

- Good Communication
- Responsible
- Attention to detail
- Teamwork
- Organizational
- Problem Solving

CERTIFICATIONS

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP)
- Credential ID: 5727875
- November 2020 November 2023

JUNIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP)
- Credential ID: 5958067
- April 2021 April 2024

PASSIONS

- Programming
- Badminton

- Gaming
- Traveling